<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Division BD</string>

    <string name="dhaka_city">Dhaka is the capital and largest city of Bangladesh.
        With its colorfoul history and rich cultural traditions, Dhaka is known the
        world over as the city of mosques and muslin. Its fame attracted travellers
        from far and near throughout the ages. Today it has grown into a mega city of
        about 16 million people, with an area of about 1353 sq. km. becoming the hub
        of the nation’s industrial, commercial, cultural, educational and political activities.

        Dhaka is located in the geographic center of the country. It is in the great deltaic
        region of the Ganges and Brahmaputra rivers. The city is within the monsoon climate zone,
        with an annual average temperature of 25 deg C (77 deg F) and monthly means varying
        between 18 deg C (64 deg F) in January and 29 deg C (84 deg F) in August. Nearly 80% of the
        annual average rainfall of 1,854 mm (73 in) occurs between May and September.

        The highlight of any visit to Dhaka is to take in a serving of the pulsing vibrancy and extraordinary
        atmosphere of Puran Dhaka (Old Dhaka). With its winding alleyways and frenetic buzzing energy,
        there is something to see around every corner and a walk here proves to be quite the photographer’s delight.
        Travel by a horse driven cart or rickshaw along busy Dhaka streets is a rewarding experience.

</string>
    <string name="chittagong_city">Chittagong is an important zone for South Asia because it
        has a major seaport which is situated in convenient geographic location. Chittagong
        is the second largest city of Bangladesh and contains most of the natural wonders of
        the country. It is situated between hill tracts and the sea bay of Bengal and in the
        bank of the river Karnaphuli.

        Though the metropolitan area is not very big but the whole division consists of a large amount
        of the rural areas, sea beach, several islands and deep hill tracts. There is a good
        communication infrastructure to reach various parts within few hours.

        The most popular natural wonders of Chittagong are cox’s bazaar, Saint Martin Island, Bandarban,
        Naval Beach and Rangamati. There are more places that you may not want to miss the chance to
        visit whenever you get. Those are Bhatiary hill, Meghla, Sitakunda Eco park, dula hajara
        safari park, foys lake, himchori, inani.

        The local culture is highly enriched in aspect of food and sociability. You will get wide variety
        of dishes all over the restaurants in Chittagong. The local inhabitants are very cordial and show
        highest hospitality to their guests.

        The accommodation facility is very satisfactory in Chittagong. There are many hotels providing quality
        services in very reasonable price. You can find some best hotels here those maintains international standard.

    </string>

    <string name="sylhet_city">Sylhet is considered one of the most picturesque and archaeologically rich
        regions in South Asia, and has major Islamic Sufi shrines. Its bourgeoning economy has contributed
        to the regional attractions of landscapes filled with fragrant orange and pineapple gardens and
        tea plantations. Many Sylheti community members are working and residing abroad, particularly in
        the United Kingdom. They send remittances to fund projects and industries within the Sylhet Division,
        which have led to the expansion of the export industry and foreign investment sectors.

     </string>

    <string name="barisal_city">Barisal District. Barisal District, officially known as Barishal District,
        is a district in south-central Bangladesh, formerly called Bakerganj district, established in 1797.
        Its headquarters are in the city of Barisal, which is also the headquarters of Barisal Division.

      </string>

    <string name="khulna_city">Khulna is an old river port located on the Rupsha River.
        It is an important hub of Bangladeshi industry and hosts many national companies.
        It is served by Port of Mongla, the second largest seaport in the country.
        It is also one of the two principal naval command centres of the Bangladesh Navy.
        Navy base BNS Titumir is located in the city.

      </string>

    <string name="rajshahi_city">Rajshahi is an important administrative, educational, cultural
         business centre in Bangladesh today. It is a historic center of silk production.
        Varendra Research Museum, which is oldest of its kind in Bangladesh is located in the city.
        The city is home to many renowned educational institutions of Bangladesh. The head office of
        Rajshahi Agricultural Development Bank and Barind Multipurpose Development Authority (BMDA)
        is situated in the city. Rajshahi is served by the Shah Makhdum Airport.

      </string>

    <string name="rangpur_city">Rangpur (Bengali: রংপুর) is one of the major cities in
        Bangladesh and Rangpur Division. Rangpur was declared a district headquarters on
        16 December 1769, and established as a municipality in 1869, making it one of the
        oldest municipalities in Bangladesh.

      </string>

    <string name="man_city">Mymensingh Division (Bengali: ময়মনসিংহ বিভাগ) is one of the eight
        administrative divisions of Bangladesh. It has an area of 10,485 km² and a population
        of 11,370,000 as of the 2011 census. It was created in 2015 from districts previously
        comprising the northern part of Dhaka Division. Its headquarters are in Mymensingh city
        in Mymensingh District.

      </string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps1">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps2">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps3">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps4">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps5">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps6">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps7">Map</string>

</resources>
